My therapist said that me being condescending
is me not choosing violence.
And I was like, correct.
I mean, I have rage, I have like real rage.
I'm paraphrasing, but James Baldwin has said,
like to live as like a conscious, alert black person
in America is to live in a constant state of rage.
Like you're always managing that.
White people know that.
That's why they say things like ,
they're like, watch, you're gonna fight me.
And you know, so sometimes you're like,
well, you're not gonna get me out of my shit
because I know what you're trying to do.
But then sometimes you're like, yeah, like, you know,
that's my favorite genre of Instagram, by the way.
Like white people getting punched for being Karens
and saying the N word.
That's .